<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="auto_door_handle_summary">Handles pop out when door unlocked</string>
    <string name="bsd_feature_help_1">If XPILOT system detects other vehicles in the rear blind spot area, the blind spot warning lights on the exterior rear-view mirrors will turn on as shown. Please avoid changing lanes if possible.\n\nBlind Spot Security assistance is an active reminder function and may cause unnecessary alarms. Drivers can decide whether to change lanes based on the actual situation.\n\nFor details, please refer to the relevant parts in the User Manual.</string>
    <string name="car_setting_door_key_tv_format">: %s</string>
    <string name="car_setting_x_key_title">Customized Key Settings</string>
    <string name="car_setting_x_key_tv_format">: %s</string>
    <string name="ciu_close_disable_for_acc">This function cannot be turned off when Assisted Driving is enabled</string>
    <string name="ciu_face_recognition_dialog_content_tv">When this feature is turned on, you can set up and use face recognition to easily switch between multiple accounts. \n\tThis will be unavailable if the feature is turned off. \n\tOnly the main account can turn this on/off.</string>
    <string name="ciu_face_recognition_tv">Face recognition</string>
    <string name="ciu_fatigue_driving_dialog_content_tv">When this feature is turned on, the system will determine whether the driver is fatigued or not based on the driving behavior and will provide alerts as necessary. \n\tThis will be unavailable if the feature is turned off.</string>
    <string name="ciu_fatigue_driving_tv">Fatigued alerts</string>
    <string name="ciu_inattention_dialog_content_tv">When this feature is turned on, the system will determine whether the driver is distracted or not based on the driving behavior and will provide alerts as necessary. \n\tThis will be unavailable if the feature is turned off.</string>
    <string name="ciu_inattention_tv">Distraction alerts</string>
    <string name="ciu_inner_camera_content_tv">Make sure that the protective film on the in-vehicle camera has been removed and the camera is not obstructed</string>
    <string name="ciu_inner_camera_dialog_content_tv">When this feature is turned off, the in-vehicle camera will stop working and all in-vehicle smart functions will be disabled, including in-vehicle LED lights, face login, fatigue detection, and distraction detection. \n\tIt is recommended to keep this feature enabled. Only the main account can turn this on/off. \n\tNote: Make sure that the protective film on the in-vehicle camera has been removed and the camera is not obstructed to improve the recognition rate.</string>
    <string name="ciu_inner_camera_feature_feedback">Turning off the in-vehicle camera will disable all in-vehicle vision functions, including distraction detection and fatigue detection.\nAre you sure you want to turn it off?</string>
    <string name="door_key_setting_vui_label">修改|修改后排车门快捷键</string>
    <string name="dow_feature_help_1">If XPILOT system detects crossing vehicles behind when parking, Door Open Warning (DOW) will turn on the blind spot warning lights on the exterior rear-view mirrors as shown in the above figure. Both the driver and passengers need to confirm whether it is safe to open the door. In this case, when trying to open the door on the side with the warning light on, sound alarms will be activated, reminding the driver or passenger of the risk.\n\nDoor Open Warning (DOW) is an active reminder function and may cause unnecessary alarms. Drivers and passengers can decide whether to open the door based on the actual situation.\n\nFor details, please refer to the relevant parts in the User Manual.</string>
    <string name="drive_mileage_since_charge">Since Last Charge</string>
    <string name="drive_mileage_since_start">Since Start</string>
    <string name="drive_mileage_title">Total</string>
    <string name="fcw_feature_help_1">Forward Collision Mitigation includes Forward Collision Warning (FCW) and Advanced Emergency Braking (AEB). \n\nXPILOT Driving Assist alerts the driver with visual and audio warnings via the dashboard when a high risk of front collision is detected. It assists the driver to brake in an emergency to avoid or reduce the impact of the front collision. \n\nWhen the Advanced Emergency Braking (AEB) is triggered, the dashboard will send the following visual warning with a short, quick sound. At the same time, the seat belt will tighten up to minimize the harm from a potential collision.</string>
    <string name="fcw_feature_help_2">Forward collision warning is a driving assistance function and is not able to avoid all collisions. Speed, weather, and tire performance affect the collision warning performance. Please keep a reasonable distance from other vehicles and drive cautiously.\n\nFor details, please refer to the relevant parts in the User Manual.</string>
    <string name="islc_feature_desc">Adjust the cruise speed based on road conditions</string>
    <string name="islc_feature_help_1">If XPILOT system detects speed limit information ahead, it will show the speed limit on the dashboard.\n\nWhen the limitation information provided by the Intelligent Speed Limit Control is inaccurate, please control the speed according to actual requirements.\n\nFor details, please refer to the relevant parts in the User Manual.</string>
    <string name="laa_feature_confirm_text">The Intelligent Cruising Assistance (ICA) and Traffic Jam Assistance (TJA) with Lane Center Control (LCC) are still driving assistance functions and cannot achieve automatic piloting of the vehicle. When using this function, the driver must focus on the road conditions and control the steering wheel (as shown in the figure below) to take over control of the vehicle at any time.</string>
    <string name="laa_feature_help_1">1. Function Activation \nWhen LCC is ready, move the shift lever downwards twice to the bottom position (i.e. the XPILOT gear) and release it to activate ACC and LCC simultaneously. In this case, the driver only needs to hold the steering wheel lightly. \n\n2. Activation Conditions \nThis function can be activated on straight roads with clear lane lines. The LCC icon on the dashboard will appear in gray, indicating that the function is ready. \nOnce the function is activated, the LCC icon will change from gray to blue. \n\n3. Function Deactivation \nTo manually deactivate LCC, move the shift lever upwards and release or press the brake pedal. The steering wheel icon on the touchscreen will turn gray, indicating that the LCC is exited. \n\n4. Parameter Adjustment \nPress the left and right arrow buttons on the left side of the steering wheel to increase and decrease the following distance. Press the up and down arrow buttons to increase and decrease the cruise speed. Press once to increase/decrease the cruise speed by 5 km/h. Press and hold to increase/decrease the speed by 1 km/h. \n\nLCC cannot realize completely automatic driving of the vehicle. Please follow local laws and regulations and keep an eye on road situation. You should cautiously use the function especially under bad weather and at intersections since XPILOT will be greatly affected in such situations.</string>
    <string name="laa_feature_help_2">When the ACC system is activated, you can turn the rod to B direction to increase maximum cruising speed, or turn it to C direction to decrease the max speed. \n\nPress brakes or turn the rod to D direction to quit ACC system. By adjusting the knob on the top of the rod, you can adjust the distance from the preceding vehicle. \n\nSafety instructions: \nACC system may fail to recognize vehicles or pedestrians that suddenly change to your lane or appear in front of the vehicle within a short distance and fail to recognize stable vehicles that are far from your vehicle. Drivers should be alert to such scenarios and take over the vehicle before potential hazards occur to avoid traffic accidents. \n\nLane Centering Control \n\nLCC system can facilitate the driver to control steering wheel and keep the vehicle in current lane. \n\nWhen the gray light indicating LCC is lit up on the dashboard, it means that LCC system is ready and you can activate it at any time. \n\nWhen LCC system is ready, turn the cruising control rod twice to A direction (see sample for ACC control rod) to start ACC and LCC simultaneously. All the driver has to do now is to hold the steering wheel. \n\nSafety instructions: \nACC and LCC cannot realize completely automatic driving of the vehicle. Please follow local laws and regulations and keep an eye on road situation. You should cautiously use these functions especially under bad weather and at intersections. Do not rely on LCC to control the steering wheel at sharp turns since XPILOT will be greatly affected in such situation. At the same time, please respond to the system\'s takeover request in time to ensure driving safety.\n\nFor details, please refer to the relevant parts in the User Manual.</string>
    <string name="laa_feature_vui_label">“LCC”</string>
    <string name="lca_feature_vui_label">ALC</string>
    <string name="ldw_feature_help_1">If XPILOT system detects that the vehicle drifts from its lane unintentionally, the lane on the dashboard will turn red as shown in the above figure with alarms to remind the driver. The seat belt will tighten up slightly and automatically for three times to keep the driver focusing on driving.\n\nLane Deviation Warning (LDW) is an active reminder function and cannot lead the vehicle to its original lane. Please adjust the vehicle\'s position when the warning occurs.\n\nFor details, please refer to the relevant parts in the User Manual.</string>
    <string name="rcta_feature_help_1">If XPILOT system detects crossing vehicles behind when reversing, the blind spot warning lights on the exterior rear-view mirrors will turn on as shown in the above figure. In this case, the driver should pay more attention to the reversing situation.\n\nRear Cross Traffic Alert (RCTA) is an active reminder function and may cause unnecessary alarms. Drivers can decide whether to continue reversing based on the actual situation.\n\nFor details, please refer to the relevant parts in the User Manual.</string>
    <string name="ready_disable_error_repair_content_common_no_nfc">Please carry the key when boarding the vehicle</string>
    <string name="x_key_setting_vui_label">修改|修改方向盘自定义按键</string>
    <string name="xpu_low_power_feature_desc">Activating the function will disable the XPILOT system.</string>
</resources>
